Contact

03063213951 (Work) zuhaibahmed3213951@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/zuhaibah (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Social Media Marketing
Digital Marketing
Online Marketing

Languages

English (Professional Working)
French (Limited Working)
Spanish (Limited Working)
German (Limited Working)
Arabic (Limited Working)

Certifications

Business communication
Certified Web Professional - Site
Designer (CWP)
Social media marketing

Zuhaib Ahmed

WordPress Specialist | Generated over 100k\$ Sales On Clients Sites | Student of GenAl, Web3 and Metaverse

Sukkur, Sindh, Pakistan

Summary

The words I use to describe myself are: creative web designer & developer with 4 years of experience in the design and customization of WordPress websites. I aim to provide highly professional, responsive, and high-quality services using my academic and professional knowledge of web design.

Experience

Fiverr

3 years 8 months

WordPress Developer | Web Developer | Web Designer April 2021 - Present (3 years 8 months)

Pakistan

Do you wanna see creativity in your website that reflects a creative and fascinating web design? I'm here to do this job for YOU. I'm a professionally trained Website Designer and Developer with three years of Amazing experience at design and customization of WordPress Sites. My service is to provide you utmost Professional, Responsive and High-quality services and features. Its guaranteed because of my academic and professional knowledge at Website development

- Website designing
- Website Maintainance
- WordPress website development
- Landing page design
- Website Security checkup
- Graphic design (banners, logos etc)

Web Designer October 2021 - October 2021 (1 month)

Banaadir, Somalia

Wordpress Developer 2022 - Present (2 years)

Sindh, Pakistan

Website Designer
Website Developer
Landing Page Designer
Elementor Expert
Ecommerce Website Development
CMS *(Learn management system)
Design

Freelancer.com
Wordpress Developer
July 2020 - Present (4 years 5 months)

Education

Governor Sindh Initiative for GenAI, Web3, and Metaverse Cloud Applied Generative AI Engineer, Artificial Intelligence